[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Переїжджати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "引っ越します"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'Відвідувати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "通います"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Сторона, бік' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "側"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'Період, час, пора' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "頃"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'слово' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "言葉"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'префікс' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "接頭辞"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'суфікс' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "接尾辞"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'велика школа' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "大学校"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'новий велосипед' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "新自転車"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'не дружній' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "不親切な"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the word 'адреса (ввічливо)' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "御住所"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the word 'лабораторія' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "研究所"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the word 'кінотеатр' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "映画館"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the word 'музикант' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "音楽家"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "How is the word 'зоопарк' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "動物園"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "How is the word 'тварина' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "動物"
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "How is the word 'парк' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "園"
    },
    {
        "id": "18",
        "question": "How is the word 'бібліотека' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "図書館"
    },
    {
        "id": "19",
        "question": "How is the word 'старий книжний' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "古本屋"
    },
    {
        "id": "20",
        "question": "How is the word 'видання газет' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "新聞社"
    },
    {
        "id": "21",
        "question": "How is the word 'не популярний' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "不有名"
    },
    {
        "id": "22",
        "question": "How is the word 'їжа, рис' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "御飯"
    },
    {
        "id": "23",
        "question": "How is the word 'не популярний' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "不人気"
    },
    {
        "id": "24",
        "question": "How is the word 'новий парк' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "新公園"
    },
    {
        "id": "25",
        "question": "How is the word 'банкір' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "銀行家"
    },
    {
        "id": "26",
        "question": "How is the word 'письменник' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "作家"
    },
    {
        "id": "27",
        "question": "How is the word 'новий твір' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "新作分"
    },
    {
        "id": "28",
        "question": "How is the word 'місце' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "所"
    },
    {
        "id": "29",
        "question": "How is the word 'Вузькі, малі місця' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "狭くて、小さいところ"
    },
    {
        "id": "30",
        "question": "How is the word 'адреса' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "住所"
    },
    {
        "id": "31",
        "question": "How is the word 'околиця' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "近所"
    },
    {
        "id": "32",
        "question": "How is the word 'визначні місця' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "名所"
    },
    {
        "id": "33",
        "question": "How is the word 'роблять особливу роботу' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "特別な仕事すること"
    },
    {
        "id": "34",
        "question": "How is the word 'лабораторія' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "研究所"
    },
    {
        "id": "35",
        "question": "How is the word 'посольство' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "市役所"
    },
    {
        "id": "36",
        "question": "How is the word 'в’язниця' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "刑務所"
    },
    {
        "id": "37",
        "question": "How is the word 'місце' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "場"
    },
    {
        "id": "38",
        "question": "How is the word 'місце, де збираються люди' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "人が集まる所です"
    },
    {
        "id": "39",
        "question": "How is the word 'зал засідань' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "会場"
    },
    {
        "id": "40",
        "question": "How is the word 'баня, душ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "浴場"
    },
    {
        "id": "41",
        "question": "How is the word 'ринок, базар' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "市場"
    },
    {
        "id": "42",
        "question": "How is the word 'щось трапляється(івенти, події)' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "何か行うことです"
    },
    {
        "id": "43",
        "question": "How is the word 'театр' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "劇場"
    },
    {
        "id": "44",
        "question": "How is the word 'зал церемонії' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "式場"
    },
    {
        "id": "45",
        "question": "How is the word 'фронт, поле бою' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "戦場"
    },
    {
        "id": "46",
        "question": "How is the word 'сторожити' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "区"
    },
    {
        "id": "47",
        "question": "How is the word 'земельні ділянки поділені' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "土地を分けたところ"
    },
    {
        "id": "48",
        "question": "How is the word 'шкільний район' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "学区"
    },
    {
        "id": "49",
        "question": "How is the word 'спеціальна зона' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "特区"
    },
    {
        "id": "50",
        "question": "How is the word 'район Шінджюку' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "新宿区"
    },
    {
        "id": "51",
        "question": "How is the word 'земля' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "地"
    },
    {
        "id": "52",
        "question": "How is the word 'земельні ділянки і поверхня землі' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "地面や土地"
    },
    {
        "id": "53",
        "question": "How is the word 'оренда землі' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "借地"
    },
    {
        "id": "54",
        "question": "How is the word 'цвинтар' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "墓地"
    },
    {
        "id": "55",
        "question": "How is the word 'скеляста місцина' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "山地"
    }
]